<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Featured on Qubit Shield</title><link>https://qubitshield.site/tags/featured/</link><description>Recent content in Featured on Qubit Shield</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Noah Erdogan</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 02:37:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qubitshield.site/tags/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Case for Quantum Encryption</title><link>https://qubitshield.site/post/case-for-quantum/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 13:35:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://qubitshield.site/post/case-for-quantum/</guid><description>The future is here already. Don&amp;rsquo;t be left behind on the wrong side of technological history. Join the future, the quantum future, with Qubit Shield.
The Quantum Problem And Our Quantum Solution Quantum Computers pose a serious threat to cyber security in the coming decade. Quantum computers can easily break classical encryption keys with relatively simple quantum algorithms, and this has been proven in multiple research papers as well as in practice.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Front Matter 🦉</title><link>https://qubitshield.site/page/hugo-front-matter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qubitshield.site/page/hugo-front-matter/</guid><description>Hugo allows you to add front matter in yaml, toml, or json to your content files. Read on to know more about predefined and user-defined front matter variables.</description></item><item><title>Noteworthy Publications in Quantum Encryption</title><link>https://qubitshield.site/page/featured_publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qubitshield.site/page/featured_publications/</guid><description>Major Publications in Quantum Encryption Many noteworthy discoveries have been made in the world of academia relating quantum encryption and security in recent years. Delve into some of the landmark papers in this field to understand the future of quantum security, and you will see that Qubit Shield is ahead of the curve.
Quantum Communication See a major publication on Quantum Communication.
Quantum Key Distribution and Quantum Internet Read about a breakthrough in Quantum Key Distribution and the Quantum Internet.</description></item><item><title>User Testimonials</title><link>https://qubitshield.site/page/user-testimonials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qubitshield.site/page/user-testimonials/</guid><description>User Testimonials See how some of our users utilize and value our products and services!
Sharon (32), Entrepeneur From San Diego, CA I&amp;rsquo;m a serial entrepeneur, and I rely heavily on Qubit Shield to future-proof my whole tech stack and data pipeline with its encryption technologies based on Quantum Key Distribution. I understand the threat of quantum cyber hacking in the near future, and I want my start-ups to be immune to this upcoming epidemic.</description></item></channel></rss>